A Guide to the Population Council records, Accession 1, RG 1 FA210
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Accession 1, 1
  - National Committee on Maternal Health (NCMH), 1958-1966; 3
    - General file, 1958-1964; 1
      - General Correspondence, 1963
        - N (Box 90, Folder 1685)
        - National Committee on Maternal Health - Administrative Material (Box 90, Folder 1686-1687)
        - National Committee on Maternal Health - Audit Reports (Box 90, Folder 1688)
        - National Committee on Maternal Health - Audit Reports - Working Copies, 1963-1964 (Box 90, Folder 1689)
        - National Committee on Maternal Health - Finances (Box 90, Folder 1690-1691)
        - National Committee on Maternal Health - Insurance (Box 90, Folder 1692)
        - O (Box 90, Folder 1693)
        - P (Box 90, Folder 1694)
        - Perinatal Research Project (Box 90, Folder 1695)
        - Planned Parenthood Federation of America (Box 90, Folder 1696-1697)
        - Planned Parenthood Federation of America - Social Research (Box 90, Folder 1698)
        - Population Association of America (Box 90, Folder 1699-1700)
        - Population Council (Box 90, Folder 1701)
        - Population Council (Box 91, Folder 1702*)
        - Q (Box 91, Folder 1703)
        - R (Box 91, Folder 1704)
        - S, 1962-1963 (Box 91, Folder 1705-1706)
        - Southwest Foundation for Research and Education (Box 91, Folder 1707-1708)
        - T (Box 91, Folder 1709-1710)
        - Thrombophlebitis Project (Box 91, Folder 1711)
        - Tietze, Christopher and Dingle, Janet - Papers - "Comparative Study of Three Contraceptive Methods..." (Box 91, Folder 1712)
        - Tietze, Christopher and Dingle, Janet - Papers - "Comparative Study of Three Contraceptive Methods..." - Worksheets (Box 91, Folder 1713-1714)
        - Tietze, Christopher - Papers - "Medical Effects of Human Reproductive Control" (Box 91, Folder 1715)
        - Tietze, Christopher - Papers - "Statistical Aspects of Contraception: Use and Effectiveness" (Box 91, Folder 1716)
        - U (Box 91, Folder 1717)
        - V (Box 91, Folder 1718)
        - Vasectomy Study - Human Betterment Association (Box 91, Folder 1719-1720)
        - W (Box 91, Folder 1721)
        - Y-Z (Box 91, Folder 1722)
      - General Correspondence, 1964
        - A, 1963-1964 (Box 92, Folder 1723)
        - American Association of Planned Parenthood. Physicians (Box 92, Folder 1724)
        - American Public Health Association, 1962-1964 (Box 92, Folder 1725-1726)
        - B (Box 92, Folder 1727)
        - C, 1963-1964 (Box 92, Folder 1728)
        - D (Box 92, Folder 1729)
        - E (Box 92, Folder 1730)
        - F, 1963-1964 (Box 92, Folder 1731)
        - Fisher, Mary - Study of Oxford City Contraceptive Clinic, 1960-1964 (Box 92, Folder 1732)
        - Fisher, Mary - Study of Oxford City Contraceptive Clinic - Data (Box 92, Folder 1733)
        - Foam Tablet Acceptability Test, 1963-1965 (Box 93, Folder 1734)
        - G, 1963-1964 (Box 93, Folder 1735-1736)
        - H, 1946 1963-1964 (Box 93, Folder 1737-1738)
        - I (Box 93, Folder 1739)
        - Indianapolis Study (Box 93, Folder 1740-1741)
        - International Planned Parenthood Federation (Box 93, Folder 1742)
        - International Planned Parenthood Federation - Medical Committee (Box 93, Folder 1743)
        - International Planned Parenthood Federation - Medical Committee - Evaluation Subcommittee - Rubber Group, 1962-1964 (Box 93, Folder 1744-1745)
        - International Planned Parenthood Federation - Western Hemisphere Region (Box 93, Folder 1746)
        - J (Box 93, Folder 1747)
        - K (Box 93, Folder 1748)
        - L, 1963-1964 (Box 93, Folder 1749)
        - M, 1963-1964 (Box 93, Folder 1750)
        - N (Box 93, Folder 1751)
        - National Cancer Institute (Box 94, Folder 1752-1753)
        - National Committee on Maternal Health - Administrative Material (Box 94, Folder 1754-1755)
        - National Committee on Maternal Health - Finances (Box 94, Folder 1756-1757)
        - National Committee on Maternal Health - Financial Statements (Box 94, Folder 1758)
        - National Committee on Maternal Health - Insurance (Box 94, Folder 1759)
        - National Committee on Maternal Health - Salaries and Taxes (Box 94, Folder 1760*)
        - Tietze, Christopher - Appointment as Lecturer at Columbia University (Box 94, Folder 1761)
        - Tietze, Christopher - Papers - "The Demographic Significance of Legal Abortion in Eastern Europe" (Box 94, Folder 1762)
    - Intrauterine Contraceptive Devices Program, 1963-1966; 2
      Consists of material relating to an evaluation of Intrauterine Contraceptive Devices (IUCD's), supervised primarily by NCMH and Population Council officials.
      Folders are arranged in alphabetical order by title.
      - Correspondence, General, 1963-1965 (Box 94, Folder 1763-1765)
      - Correspondence, General, 1964-1966 (Box 95, Folder 1766-1769)
      - Correspondence - Conferences - Conference on Intrauterine Contraception May, 1964 (Box 95, Folder 1770)
      - Correspondence - Conferences - Second International Conference on the IUCD October, 1964 (Box 95, Folder 1771)
      - Correspondence - Population Council, 1964-1966 (Box 95, Folder 1772-1773)
      - Correspondence - Studies - Indianapolis Study, 1964 (Box 95, Folder 1774)
      - Evaluation - Congenital Malformations, 1966 (Box 95, Folder 1775-1776)
      - Evaluation - Cooperative Study of IUCD's, California, 1964 (Box 95, Folder 1777)
      - Evaluation - Expulsion/Possible Perforations (Box 95, Folder 1778)
      - Evaluation - Pelvic Inflammatory Disease, 1964-1966 (Box 95, Folder 1779-1780)
      - Evaluation - Perforation, 1965-1966 (Box 95, Folder 1781*)
      - Evaluation - Racial Distribution of Patients, 1965 (Box 96, Folder 1782-1783)
      - Evaluation - Recommended Procedures for the Computation of Net Cumulative Event and Closure Rates Based on All Segments, 1967 (Box 96, Folder 1784)
      - Evaluation - Serious Complications Suffered by IUCD Wearers, 1964 (Box 96, Folder 1785-1786)
      - Evaluation - Statistics - Progress Reports; Rounds Two-Six - Service Bureau Corporation, 1963-1965 (Box 96, Folder 1787-1790)
      - Evaluation - Unnoticed Expulsions of Loops, 1966 (Box 96, Folder 1791)
  - Organization File, 1956-1966; 4
    Consists of correspondence and some reports relating to the dissemination of information on population problems, coordination of educational and research activities among various organizations, grants given to and by the Population Council, and population policies of the United Nations and the United States government.
    Important files include those for the Ford Foundation, the Rockefeller Foundation, the United Nations, and the United States government.
    Arranged in alphabetical order by name of organization.
    Former Classification: IV 3B 04.5
    Related Materials
    See also: FA432 Population Council records, Accession 2, Series 1: Organization File, for records dating from 1967-1976.
    Indexing to the Organization File is provided by FA775 Population Council records, Index, Series 2: Central File Index, 1961-1976.
    - Agricultural Development Council, 1963-1966 (Box 97, Folder 1792-1793)
    - Alfred P. Sloane Foundation, 1958-1960 (Box 97, Folder 1794)
    - American Academy of Political and Social Sciences, 1964-1966 (Box 97, Folder 1795)
    - American Eugenics Society, 1965-1966 (Box 97, Folder 1976)
    - American Eugenics Society - Fertility of Handicapped - Kirk, Dudley, 1956-1960 (Box 97, Folder 1977)
    - American Friends Service Committee, 1963-1966 (Box 97, Folder 1798-1799)
    - American Institutes for Research, 1965-1966 (Box 97, Folder 1800)
    - American Medical Association, 1963-1966 (Box 97, Folder 1801)
    - American Public Health Association, 1962-1966 (Box 97, Folder 1802)
    - American Public Health Association - Meeting, 1966 (Box 97, Folder 1803)
    - American Sociological Association, 1963-1966 (Box 97, Folder 1804)
    - American Statistical Association, 1963-1966 (Box 97, Folder 1805-1806)
    - American Statistical Association - Committee on Fellows, 1963 (Box 97, Folder 1807)
    - American University, 1963-1965 (Box 97, Folder 1808-1809)
    - Asia Foundation, 1963-1966 (Box 97, Folder 1810)
    - Asia Society, 1963-1966 (Box 97, Folder 1811)
    - Association for Voluntary Sterilization, 1965-1966 (Box 98, Folder 1812)
    - Association of American Medical Colleges, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 1813)
    - Avalon Foundation, 1959-1963 (Box 98, Folder 1814)
    - Baltimore - Health Department, 1963-1965 (Box 98, Folder 1815-1816)
    - Baylor University, 1963-1966 (Box 98, Folder 1817-1818)
    - Boston University, 1963-1965 (Box 98, Folder 1819)
    - Brown University, 1963-1966 (Box 98, Folder 1820-1821)
    - Brown University - Grant Proposal, 1963 (Box 98, Folder 1822)
    - Brown University - Potter, Robert, 1963-1966 (Box 98, Folder 1823)
    - Bucknell University, 1964 (Box 98, Folder 1824)
    - California - Department of Public Health, 1963-1965 (Box 98, Folder 1825-1826)
    - Carnegie Corporation of New York, 1959-1965 (Box 98, Folder 1827)
    - Case Institute of Technology, 1965 (Box 98, Folder 1828)
    - Catholic Committee on Population and Government Policy, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 1829)
    - Catholic Family Information Service - Cana Conference Film on Rhythm Method, 1965 (Box 98, Folder 1830-1831)
    - Charles S. Mott Foundation, 1964-1967 (Box 98, Folder 1832)
    - China Medical Board, Incorporated, 1963 (Box 98, Folder 1833)
    - Church World Service, 1965-1966 (Box 98, Folder 1834)
    - Columbia University, 1963-1966 (Box 98, Folder 1835-1836)
    - Columbia University - American Assembly - President's Commission on National Goals, 1960 (Box 98, Folder 1837)
    - Columbia University - Jaffe, Abram, 1964-1966 (Box 98, Folder 1838)
    - Columbia University - Teachers College, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 1839)
    - Commission of the Churches on International Affairs, 1963-1966 (Box 98, Folder 1840)
    - Commonwealth Fund, 1957-1966 (Box 99, Folder 1841)
    - Conservation Foundation, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 1842)
    - Cornell University, 1963-1966 (Box 99, Folder 1843)
    - Cornell University - Hassan, S. S., 1964 (Box 99, Folder 1844*)
    - Cornell University - Stycos, J. Mayone, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 1845)
    - Council on Economic and Cultural Affairs, 1963 (Box 99, Folder 1846)
    - Council on Foreign Relations, 1963 (Box 99, Folder 1847)
    - Draper Committee, 1959 (Box 99, Folder 1848-1849)
    - Duke University, 1963-1966 (Box 99, Folder 1850-1851)
    - Earl Newsom and Company, 1963-1966 (Box 99, Folder 1852)
    - Emory University, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 1853)
    - Florida State University, 1962-1966 (Box 99, Folder 1854-1855)
    - Ford Foundation
      - General Material, 1959-1966 (Box 99, Folder 1856-1859)
      - General Material, 1960-1966 (Box 100, Folder 1860-1861)
      - Funds - Cargille, Charles, 1959 (Box 100, Folder 1862-1863)
      - Grants - Population Council, 1957-1963 (Box 100, Folder 1864)
      - Grants - Population Council Expansion, 1960-1966 (Box 100, Folder 1865)
      - Grants - Population Council Expansion - Biomedical Division, 1965 (Box 100, Folder 1866)
      - Institute for the Study of Human Reproduction, 1963-1965 (Box 100, Folder 1867)
      - Physiology of Reproduction Survey, 1960-1961 (Box 100, Folder 1868-1869)
      - Proposed Program in Population Problems, 1959 (Box 100, Folder 1870)
      - Southeast Asia Mission (with Population Council), 1962-1963 (Box 100, Folder 1871-1872)
      - Worcester Foundation for Experimental Biology - Training Program in Reproductive Physiology, 1960-1964 (Box 100, Folder 1873)
    - Fordham University - Interdisciplinary Seminar on Population, 1960 (Box 100, Folder 1874)
    - Foreign Policy Association, 1964-1966 (Box 100, Folder 1875-1876)
    - Foundation for Reproductive Research, 1964 (Box 100, Folder 1877)
    - Foundation Group, 1963-1966 (Box 100, Folder 1878)
    - Foundation Library Center, 1965-1966 (Box 100, Folder 1879)
    - Gallup Organization - Opinion Survey, 1965-1966 (Box 100, Folder 1880)
    - George Washington University, 1963-1966 (Box 100, Folder 1881)
    - Georgetown University, 1963-1966 (Box 100, Folder 1882)
    - Gleich Foundation, 1959-1966 (Box 100, Folder 1883)
    - Harvard University
      - General Material, 1963-1966 (Box 101, Folder 1884-1885)
      - Center for Population Studies - School of Public Health, 1963-1966 (Box 101, Folder 1886)
      - Round Table Discussion - Mauldin, W. Parker, 1961 (Box 101, Folder 1887)
      - Snyder, John C., 1963-1966 (Box 101, Folder 1888-1889)
      - Wyon, John, 1963-1965 (Box 101, Folder 1890-1891)
    - Hohabe, Incorporated, 1965-1966 (Box 101, Folder 1892)
    - Hugh Moore Fund, 1959-1966 (Box 101, Folder 1893)
    - Human Betterment Association of America, 1964 (Box 101, Folder 1894)
    - Indiana University, 1963-1966 (Box 101, Folder 1895)
    - Informatics, Incorporated, 1966 (Box 101, Folder 1896)
    - Information Center on Population Problems, 1964-1966 (Box 101, Folder 1897-1898)
    - Interagency Group of Family Planning Workers, 1966 (Box 101, Folder 1899)
    - Inter-American Statistical Institute, 1963-1965 (Box 101, Folder 1900)
    - International Affairs Seminar of Washington, 1960 (Box 101, Folder 1901)
    - International Bank for Reconstruction and Development, 1959-1963 (Box 101, Folder 1902-1903)
    - International Conference on Medical Librarian ship (Second), 1961 (Box 101, Folder 1904)
    - International Indian Ocean Expedition, 1958-1960 (Box 101, Folder 1905-1906)
    - International Institute of Education, 1963-1966 (Box 101, Folder 1907)
    - International Planned Parenthood Federation - Western Hemisphere Region, 1965-1966 (Box 101, Folder 1908)
    - International Planned Parenthood Federation - Western Hemisphere Region, 1965-1966 (Box 102, Folder 1909)
    - International Social Science Council, 1964 (Box 102, Folder 1910)
    - International Union for the Scientific Study of Population (Box 102, Folder 1911)
      - General Material, 1961-1965 (Box 102, Folder 1912)
      - Members and Regions, 1959-1965 (Box 102, Folder 1913)
      - Population Conference (with Population Council), 1961 (Box 102, Folder 1914)
      - Population - New York City, 1957-1961 1965 (Box 102, Folder 1915-1918)
      - Sydney Conference on Population Issues in Asia and the Far East, 1966 (Box 103, Folder 1919-1920)
    - Japan Society, 1965 (Box 103, Folder 1921)
    - John and Mary R. Markle Foundation, 1963 (Box 103, Folder 1922)
    - John D. Rockefeller 3rd Fund, 1964 (Box 103, Folder 1923)
    - John Lindsley Fund, 1964-1965 (Box 103, Folder 1924)
    - Johns Hopkins University, 1963-1966 (Box 103, Folder 1925-1927)
    - Johns Hopkins University - Harper, Paul, 1963-1966 (Box 103, Folder 1928-1930)
    - Johns Hopkins University - Joint Section on Population - Proposal, 1963-1964 (Box 103, Folder 1931-1932)
    - Johnson Foundation, 1965 (Box 103, Folder 1933-1934)
    - Lalor Foundation, 1963-1966 (Box 103, Folder 1935)
    - League of Women Voters, 1965 (Box 103, Folder 1936)
    - Le Moyne College, 1963 (Box 103, Folder 1937-1938)
    - Louisiana State University, 1963-1966 (Box 103, Folder 1939)
    - Macy Foundation, 1965-1966 (Box 103, Folder 1940)
    - Margaret Sanger Research Bureau, 1963-1966 (Box 104, Folder 1941-1942)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1965-1966 (Box 104, Folder 1943)
    - Miami University (Ohio), 1963-1964 (Box 104, Folder 1944)
    - Miami University (Ohio) - Scripps Foundation for Population Problems, 1963-1964 (Box 104, Folder 1945)
    - Michigan State University, 1963-1966 (Box 104, Folder 1946-1947)
    - Middle East Institute, 1965-1966 (Box 104, Folder 1948)
    - Milbank Memorial Fund
      - General Material, 1963-1966 (Box 104, Folder 1949-1950)
      - Family Planning Conference (with Population Council), 1959-1964 (Box 104, Folder 1951-1953)
      - Family Planning Conference (with Population Council) Mailing List, 1961-1962 (Box 104, Folder 1954)
      - Family Planning Conference (with Population Council) Participants (A-J), 1960 (Box 104, Folder 1955-1956)
      - Family Planning Conference (with Population Council) Participants (K-Z), 1960 (Box 105, Folder 1957-1959)
      - Princeton University and Office of Population Research - Fertility, 1959-1960 (Box 105, Folder 1960)
    - Miscellaneous Organizations, 1966 (Box 105, Folder 1961)
    - Mount Sinai Hospital, 1966 (Box 105, Folder 1962)
    - National Academy of Sciences, 1963-1966 (Box 105, Folder 1963)
    - National Academy of Sciences - Latin American Science Board, 1964-1965 (Box 105, Folder 1964-1965)
    - National Catholic Welfare Conference, 1962 (Box 105, Folder 1966)
    - National Committee on Maternal Health - Tietze, Christopher, 1960-1966 (Box 105, Folder 1967-1970)
    - National Committee on Maternal Health - Vasectomy Study, 1957 (Box 105, Folder 1971)
    - National Science Foundation, 1963-1966 (Box 106, Folder 1972)
    - National Urban League, 1965-1966 (Box 106, Folder 1973)
    - New York University, 1963-1966 (Box 106, Folder 1974)
    - Northwestern University, 1966 (Box 106, Folder 1975)
    - Ohio State University, 1966 (Box 106, Folder 1976)
    - Oklahoma State University, 1963 (Box 106, Folder 1977-1978)
    - Old Dominion Foundation, 1962 (Box 106, Folder 1979)
    - Pan American Health Organization, 1964-1966 (Box 106, Folder 1980-1983)
    - Pan American Union, 1964-1966 (Box 106, Folder 1984)
    - Pathfinder Fund, 1963-1965 (Box 106, Folder 1985)
    - Pathfinder Fund, 1964-1966 (Box 107, Folder 1986-1987)
    - Pennsylvania State University, 1966 (Box 107, Folder 1988)
    - Planned Parenthood Association - Chicago Area, 1966 (Box 107, Folder 1989)
    - Planned Parenthood Federation of America, 1963 (Box 107, Folder 1990-1992)
    - Planned Parenthood Kershaw County (South Carolina) Grant Proposal, 1963 (Box 107, Folder 1993)
    - Planned Parenthood - World Population, 1963-1966 (Box 107, Folder 1994-1998)
    - Planned Parenthood - World Population, 1964-1967 (Box 108, Folder 1999-2000)
    - Planned Parenthood - World Population - Grant Proposal - Research Aspect of Family Planning Service, 1964 (Box 108, Folder 2001)
    - Population Association of America, 1963-1966 (Box 108, Folder 2002-2004)
    - Population Association of America - Meetings, 1958-1966 (Box 108, Folder 2005)
    - Population Crisis Committee, 1965-1966 (Box 108, Folder 2006)
    - Population Reference Bureau, 1963-1966 (Box 108, Folder 2005-2009)
    - Population Reference Bureau - Latin American Department, 1966 (Box 109, Folder 2010)
    - Princeton University, 1963-1965 (Box 109, Folder 2011)
    - Princeton University - African Studies - Lorimer, Frank, 1960-1962 (Box 109, Folder 2012-2013)
    - Princeton University - Office of Population Research, 1963-1966 (Box 109, Folder 2014)
    - Princeton University - Office of Population Research - Westoff, Charles, 1963-1966 (Box 109, Folder 2015)
    - Public Affairs Commission, 1966 (Box 109, Folder 2016)
    - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, 1958-1966 (Box 109, Folder 2017-2018)
    - Rockefeller Foundation
      - General Material, 1959-1966 (Box 109, Folder 2019-2021)
      - Balfour, Marshall C.- India, 1958-1961 (Box 109, Folder 2022-2023)
      - Balfour, Marshall C.- New York, 1959-1961 (Box 109, Folder 2024-2025)
      - Fellowship Program, 1958-1966 (Box 110, Folder 2026)
      - La Montagne, Raymond, 1965-1966 (Box 110, Folder 2027)
    - Rosenstock Foundation, Incorporated, 1962-1963 (Box 110, Folder 2028)
    - Russell Sage Foundation, 1965-1966 (Box 110, Folder 2029)
    - Rutgers University, 1963-1964 (Box 110, Folder 2030)
    - Saint Lawrence University, 1964-1965 (Box 110, Folder 2031-2032)
    - Salisbury Community Fund, 1962-1966 (Box 110, Folder 2033)
    - San Diego State College, 1963 (Box 110, Folder 2034)
    - Scholastic Research Center, 1966 (Box 110, Folder 2035)
    - Science Information Exchange, 1966 (Box 110, Folder 2036)
    - Science Service, 1966 (Box 110, Folder 2037)
    - Seton Hall College of Medicine and Dentistry, 1963 (Box 110, Folder 2038-2039)
    - Social Science Research Council, 1963-1966 (Box 110, Folder 2040)
    - Social Science Research Council - Demographic Conference (with Population Council), 1961-1964 (Box 110, Folder 2041)
    - Society for International Development, 1966 (Box 110, Folder 2042-2043)
    - Society for the Scientific Study of Sex, 1964-1966 (Box 110, Folder 2044)
    - Sports International, 1965-1966 (Box 110, Folder 2045)
    - Stanford University, 1963-1966 (Box 110, Folder 2046)
    - State University of New York, 1964-1966 (Box 110, Folder 2047-2048)
    - Sunnen Products Company, 1959 1963-1964 (Box 110, Folder 2049-2050)
    - Temple University, 1965 (Box 110, Folder 2051)
    - Tulane University, 1965 (Box 110, Folder 2052)
    - Unitarian Universalist Service Committee, Incorporated, 1964-1965 (Box 110, Folder 2053)
    - United Nations
      - Census - Punched Cards, 1960-1962 (Box 110, Folder 2054)
      - Census Bureau, 1957-1958 (Box 110, Folder 2055-2056)
      - Children's Fund (UNICEF), 1965-1966 (Box 111, Folder 2057)
      - Demographic Training and Research Centre, 1958-1965 (Box 111, Folder 2058-2060)
      - Demographic Training and Research Centre - Bogue, Donald, 1958-1965 (Box 111, Folder 2061-2062)
      - Demographic Training and Research Centre - Bombay, 1959-1962 (Box 111, Folder 2063)
      - Demographic Training and Research Centre - Bombay Seminar, 1960 (Box 111, Folder 2064)
      - Demographic Training and Research Centre - Chandrasekaran, C., 1959-1965 (Box 111, Folder 2065-2067)
      - Demographic Training and Research Centre - Progress Reports, 1958-1963 (Box 112, Folder 2068-2070)
      - Demographic Training and Research Centre - Sills, David, 1960-1961 (Box 112, Folder 2071-2072)
      - Economic and Social Affairs, 1964 (Box 112, Folder 2073)
      - Economic Commission for Africa, 1964-1966 (Box 112, Folder 2074)
      - Economic Commission for Africa - Grant Proposal - Som, Ranjan Kumar, 1964 (Box 112, Folder 2075)
      - Economic Commission for Asia and the Far East, 1959-1966 (Box 112, Folder 2076)
      - Educational, Scientific and Cultural Organization (UNESCO), 1959-1966 (Box 112, Folder 2077)
      - Food and Agriculture Organization (FAO), 1965-1966 (Box 112, Folder 2078)
      - Miscellany - (Includes World Leaders' Statement on Population), 1966 (Box 112, Folder 2079)
      - Population Branch, 1959-1966 (Box 112, Folder 2080-2082)
      - Population Division, 1966 (Box 112, Folder 2083)
      - Reports, Studies, Correspondence, 1959-1966 (Box 113, Folder 2084-2085)
      - World Health Organization (WHO), 1958-1966 (Box 113, Folder 2086-2088)
      - World Population Conference, 1965 1962-1966 (Box 113, Folder 2089-2092)
    - United States
      - Agency for International Development, 1961-1964 (Box 113, Folder 2093)
      - Agency for International Development, 1964-1966 (Box 114, Folder 2094-2098)
      - Agency for International Development - Baumgartner, Leona, 1963-1966 (Box 114, Folder 2099-2100)
      - Agency for International Development - Population Council Assistance, 1965-1966 (Box 114, Folder 2101-2102)
      - Agency for International Development - Population Council Assistance - Bureau for Latin America, 1965-1966 (Box 114, Folder 2103)
      - Bureau of the Census, 1963-1966 (Box 115, Folder 2104-2106)
      - Congress - House of Representatives, 1960-1966 (Box 115, Folder 2107)
      - Congress - Senate, 1963-1966 (Box 115, Folder 2108-2109)
    - United States
      - Congress - Senate Reorganization Subcommittee, 1959-1960 (Box 115, Folder 2110)
      - Department of Agriculture, 1964-1966 (Box 115, Folder 2111)